<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!DOCTYPE jHelp SYSTEM "help.dtd">
<jHelp>
	<Page Path="/xapsweb/web">
		<Field ID="name">
			<Heading>
				Name 
            </Heading>
			<Help>
				Name of the file
            </Help>
		</Field>
		<Field ID="versionnumber">
			<Heading>
				Version 
            </Heading>
			<Help>
				The version is a string. The version must be unique within the File Type in this Unit Type. If the File Type
				is SOFTWARE or TR069_SCRIPT then the version number must match exactly whatever you upload to the device. Check
				help on the File Type.
            </Help>
		</Field>
		<Field ID="targetname">
			<Heading>
				Target Name
			</Heading>
			<Help>
				A target name must be specified for a TR069_SCRIPT, because it will be used in the provisiniong to separate between multiple
				script file in the same device. When the device has applied the TR069_SCRIPT file, it must use this target name as the name
				of the so-called "ConfigFile"
			</Help>
		</Field>
		<Field ID="type">
			<Heading>
				Type 
            </Heading>
			<Help>
				Currently the system supports 5 types of files:&lt;p&gt;
				SOFTWARE - Usually a firmware image for a CPE. The firmware version
				number must match the version number of the file&lt;p&gt;
				SHELL_SCRIPT - A FreeACS Shell Script, upload here to be able to run 
				it as part of a Job, Syslog Event or a Trigger. The file will be modified 
				to include your username, so the ShellDaemon running the script
				will run with the correct access rights.&lt;p&gt;
				TR069_SCRIPT - A Script/Config-file which can be sent to
				a CPE using TR069. This script/config must then modify the parameter
				InternetGatewayDevice.DeviceInfo.&lt;br&gt;VendorConfigFile.{i}.Version to match
				the version number of the file.&lt;p&gt;
				TELNET_SCRIPT - A Telnet script file, only to be used in a Job (of type 'Telnet').
				The script will execute on the CPE, and can be used to change and even
				extract data from the CPE.&lt;p&gt;
				UNITS - This file *should* only contain unitIds. So far the usage is 
				for Triggers which make a file for each Trigger Release to accompany a
				possible Trigger Shell Script, to make it possible to modify or act 
				on each CPE which was part of a Trigger Release.&lt;p&gt;
				MISC - A filetype without any special purpose. &lt;p&gt;
            </Help>
		</Field>
	</Page>
</jHelp>