<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!DOCTYPE jHelp SYSTEM "help.dtd">
<jHelp>
	<Page Path="/xapsweb/web">
		<Field ID="name">
            <Heading>Name</Heading>
            <Help>
                The name of the trigger
            </Help>
		</Field>
        <Field ID="description">
            <Heading>Description</Heading>
            <Help>
                Provide a description to help identify the trigger in future listings.
            </Help>
        </Field>
        <Field ID="typeTrigger">
            <Heading>Type</Heading>
            <Help>
                BASIC: Must specify a syslog event and "Number of"-fields. If the syslog events occur as
                specified by the "Number of"-fields within the Evaluation Period, then the trigger is released.  
                &lt;p&gt;
                COMPOSITE: If a child triggers (BASIC or COMPOSITE triggers) are released within the Evaluation Period,
                then the trigger is released.
            </Help>
        </Field>
        <Field ID="notifyType">
            <Heading>Notify Type</Heading>
            <Help>
            	REPORT: A message will be sent to the list of users in "ToList" field if the trigger is released. The
            	report will be sent every as often as the field Notify Interval indicate. The report will then contain
            	a summary of all the trigger releases since last message.
            	&lt;p&gt;
            	ALARM: Just like REPORT, but it will not be sent regularly on Notify Interval unless there was a 
            	trigger release at that time.
            	&lt;p&gt;
            	SILENT: No message 
            </Help>
        </Field>
        <Field ID="syslogEventId">
            <Heading>Syslog Event Id</Heading>
            <Help>
                Choose a syslog event if the trigger is of BASIC type.  
            </Help>
        </Field>
        <Field ID="groupId">
            <Heading>Group</Heading>
            <Help>
                Choose a group to narrow down which devices should be counted.
            </Help>
        </Field>
        <Field ID="parentTrigger">
            <Heading>Parent Trigger</Heading>
            <Help>
                Choose a COMPOSITE trigger as parent, it will then only be released if this trigger and all other
                child trigger are released within Evalution Period.
            </Help>
        </Field>
        <Field ID="toList">
            <Heading>To List</Heading>
            <Help>
                A list of comma-separated e-mail addresses the trigger will report to. If omitted the e-mail list specified
                in the propertyfile of the Monitor-server will be used.
            </Help>
        </Field>
        <Field ID="evalPeriodMinutes">
            <Heading>Evaluation Period (Minutes)</Heading>
            <Help>
                The Evaluation Period Minutes field allows a configurable timeframe to be set.
                This timeframe states that a configurable number of events must be caught within it,
                in order for the trigger to be fired.
                Example: 10 events within 15 minutes.
            </Help>
        </Field>
        <Field ID="noTotal">
            <Heading>Number of total events</Heading>
            <Help>
                The number of total events that have to sent (within the timeframe given in the Evaluation Period above) before the trigger should fire.
            </Help>
        </Field>
        <Field ID="noPrUnit">
            <Heading>Number of events per unit</Heading>
            <Help>
                The number of total events that have to sent per unit (within the timeframe given in the Evaluation Period above) before the trigger should fire.
            </Help>
        </Field>
        <Field ID="noUnits">
            <Heading>Number of Units</Heading>
            <Help>
                The number of units that have to be affected (within the timeframe given in the Evaluation Period above) before the trigger should fire.
            </Help>
        </Field> 
        <Field ID="notifyIntervalHours">
        	<Heading>Notify Interval (Hours)</Heading>
        	<Help>
        		The number of hours that must pass before a new notification is sent.
        	</Help>
        </Field>  
        <Field ID="scriptFileId">
        	<Heading>Script File</Heading>
        	<Help>
        		A script file which will be run on every trigger release. The script file will have the opportunity to process the list
        		of units which triggered the release, using a special variable ${_1} in the script. 
        	</Help>
        </Field>
        <Field ID="active">
        	<Heading>Active</Heading>
        	<Help>
        		Activate or deactivate trigger. A deactivated trigger behaves like a non-existent trigger and has no effect on the release of parent triggers.
        	</Help>
        </Field>
    </Page>
</jHelp>
